God's victorious!
Your mighty right hand, O Lord full of power
It shatters the foe, in judgment devoured
Your majesty's great, You rise and prevail
Your fury consumes; the wicked assail
The enemy boasted, “I’ll chase and destroy,
I’ll take what I want and carry my ploy
I’ll draw my sharp sword and bring them to shame”
But You blew Your wind; they sank at Your name
God's victorious, His people He saved
God's victorious, no more enslaved
God's victorious, the rivals He razed
God's victorious, triumphant and worthy of praise
The nations have heard and trembled with fear,
They shake and they scatter as judgment draws near
Dread and great terror fall down from Your throne
They freeze before You, like a rigid stone
You'll bring Your people with sovereign grace
You'll plant their feet in Your dwelling place
The mountain You formed, Your holy abode
There You will reign, with glory untold
God's victorious, His people He saved
God's victorious, no more enslaved
God's victorious, the rivals He razed
God's victorious, triumphant and worthy of praise
Who is like You, O Lord on high?
In power majestic, none can deny
Awesome in wonders, Your name is renowned,
You stretched out Your hand, the enemy drowned
God's victorious, His people He saved
God's victorious, no more enslaved
God's victorious, the rivals He razed
God's victorious, triumphant and worthy of praise
Triumphant and worthy of praise
God's victorious
He's victorious,
Victorious!